{"data":[{"question":"Had the committee members considered the alternatives more carefully, they would have realized that the second was better as the first.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were troubling","b":"to see about","c":"them","d":"pull","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Pull->pulled\nHave something done","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Malnutrition is a major cause of death in those countries where the cultivation of rice have been impeded by recurrent drought.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Hardly he had","b":"the office","c":"that he had","d":"forgotten his","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Hardly he had-> Hardly had he","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The decision to withdraw all support from the activities of the athletes are causing an uproar among the athletes' fans.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had","b":"to change","c":"hopes to be","d":"to a good university","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- To change-> change","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Underutilized species of fish has been proposed as a solution to the famine in many underdeveloped countries.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"told","b":"to don't","c":"discuss","d":"with each other","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- To don't discuss-> not to discuss","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"John's wisdom teeth were troubling him, so he went to a dental surgeon to see about having them pull.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are extremely","b":"anothers","c":"regularly","d":"many other foods","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Anothers-> others","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Hardly he had entered the office when he realized that he had forgotten his wallet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Most","b":"without","c":"a","d":"working at","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Working at-> working","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Sury had better to change her study habits if she hopes to be admitted to a good university.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"long","c":"a","d":"it is very cruel","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- It is very cruel-> cruelty","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher told the students to don't discuss the take-home exam with each other.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"All","b":"theirselves","c":"the","d":"living","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Theirselves-> themselves","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Some bacteria are extremely harmful, but anothers are regularly used in producing cheeses, crackers, and many other foods.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"had known","b":"the","c":"will receive","d":"the","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Will receive-> would receive","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Most Americans would not be happy without a color television, two cars, and working at an extra job.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has written","b":"books of poetry","c":"a biography","d":"several novel","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Several novel-> several novels","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"}]}